# **Temitope Joseph Orubuloye**

(+234) 90781237851, (+234) 07025715756  $\cdot$  Temitopeorubuloye3@gmail.com Church road kabala doki, Kaduna, Nigeria

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Knowledgeable Computer Operator, effective at setting controls and running specific daily tasks. Collaborative and communicative with proven history of quickly fixing minor issues and helping resolve more advanced problems. Meticulous in data management procedures. Dependable Computer Operator specializes in accepting, transmitting and storing sensitive customer data. Maintains strict adherence to applicable regulatory and legal requirements to mitigate risk and liability.

### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Customer Service Information Analysis Strong interpersonal skills

File Transfer Critical thinking skills Blogging

Website Development Excellent communication skills Website Modification

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### **Emperior Concepts**

Blogger / SEO content Writer

Worked as a blogger and a search engine optimization(SEO) content writer

### **Fina white House Hotels**

February 2020 - November 2022

November 2022 - Till date2

Receptionist Receptionist

Worked with Excel and registration of clients as a front desk attendant (Receptionist)

### **Khemsafe Computer Institute**

April 2017 - September 2017

**Tech student** 

Studied Basics of website development, graphic designs, as a student

# Bindave Machine/computer operator

March 2013 - September 2016

Prepared and served a variety of beverages with precision and creativity, consistently meeting or exceeding quality standards, and receiving compliments for latte art and presentation.

## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

### Federal Polytechnic kaura Namoda

Ordinary National Diploma

### Louisana De prince

Secondary

### St. Michaels / First African

NurseryPrimary

# **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

### **Asap Prime Tech Agency**

Web developer, Graphic Designer and social media manager

Emperor Concepts

Blogger / SEO content Writer